Mystic River Watershed Association Records MS055
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Mystic River Watershed Association Records
1967 -- 2001
1920 -- 2007
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Mystic River Watershed Association
MS055
52.45 Linear Feet
1 Digital Object(s) 1 zip file comprising 17 PDFs and 2 ISO files.
155.7 Megabytes
Arrangement
This collection is organized into eight series: Newsletter; Geographic subject files; General subject files; Maps; MRWA correspondence; MRWA office files; MRWA culture; General subject files.
Custodial History
In 2001, the MRWA entered into an agreement with Tufts University to house its records at the Tufts and make them available to researchers.
Scope and Contents
The Mystic River Watershed Association (MRWA) records cover a wide range of material of interest for Watershed residents, researchers, historians, and others. Topics include watershed quality, such as runoff and eutrophication as well as topics of more general relevance, such as traffic and birdwatching. Of particular interest is the extensive selection of documents pertaining to the construction of the Alewife MBTA station in the 1980s. One particularly notable feature of the collection is that it contains reports, correspondence, articles, brochures, legal documents and maps created not only by the MRWA but by related relevant organizations, such as the Environmental Protection Agency and the Joint Regional Transit Committee.
Biographical / Historical
The Mystic River Watershed Association was incorporated in 1972 to protect, restore and conserve the Mystic River, its tributaries and watershed lands. In the 1990's, the Association's charter was changed to include local groups as well as individual members. In late 1997, MRWA became a leading force in the formation of an independent watershed-wide coalition of citizens' groups.
In 2001, the MRWA entered into an agreement with Tufts University to house its records at the Tufts and make them available to researchers. The MRWA and Tufts are actively involved in the Mystic Watershed Collaborative, whose goal is to develop greater awareness and understanding of important environmental problems in our bioregion which affect human health and quality of life
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research. This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Rivers; Mystic River (Mass.); Environmental history; Maps (documents); Mystic River Watershed Association
- Newsletters, 1971 -- 2000; MS055.001; 0.25 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains periodic updates issued by the MRWA to its members. There are two distinct types of update: the Newsletter (also known as Mystic Watershed News, Recharge, and the Mystic Messenger), which contains general information about MRWA activities; and the 208 News on Water Quality Planning, last issued in November 1977. In addition, there are several smaller communications from the MRWA to its members in the form of meeting reminders and dues schedules.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Newsletters, 1971 -- 1981; MS055.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Newsletters, 1981 -- 1995; MS055.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Newsletters, 1996 -- 2000; MS055.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Newsletters, 1993 -- 1999; MS055.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
- Geographic subject files, 1965 -- 2007; 1970 -- 1985; MS055.002; 21.0 Linear Feet
  This series contains information about various cities, dams, lakes, regions, and other geographical components of the Mystic River Watershed. It contains reports, correspondence, newsclippings, maps, and related notes.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by region.
  - Aberjona River, 1973 -- 1991; MS055.002.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Aberjona River Basin quality summary, 1967 -- 1985; MS055.002.002.00002 (Box 2)
    August 1980
  - Report on Aberjona River, Winchester Mass, 1967 -- 1985; MS055.002.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Alewife Brook, 1967 -- 1985; MS055.002.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Alewife documents, 1967 -- 1985; MS055.002.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Alewife interim access, 1967 -- 1985; MS055.002.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Alewife - Linear Park, 1967 -- 1985; MS055.002.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Clean Water Week - Alewife tours, 1967 -- 1985; MS055.002.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Alewife - transit devel. + related matters (DiGiovanni), 1967 -- 1985; MS055.002.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Arlington (1), 1967 -- 1987; MS055.002.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Arlington (2), 1971 -- 1989; MS055.002.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Arlington Reservoir, 1967 -- 1985; MS055.002.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - Arlington Reservoir Beach project, 1967 -- 1985; MS055.002.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - Belmont, 1971 -- 1983; MS055.002.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - Belmont open space plant inventory, 1973 -- 1979; MS055.002.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - Blair Pond, 1970 -- 1993; MS055.002.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - The state of Boston Harbor, 1970 -- 1993; MS055.002.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - Boston and harbor, 1970 -- 1993; MS055.002.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - Burlington, 1978 -- 1979; MS055.002.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - Cambridge, 1973 -- 1984; MS055.002.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - Chelsea (1), 1970 -- 1993; MS055.002.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - Chelsea (2), 1970 -- 1993; MS055.002.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - Craddock Dam, 1970 -- 1993; MS055.002.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Earhart Dam, 1970 -- 1993; MS055.002.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - East Boston, 1970 -- 1993; MS055.002.004.00005 (Box 4)
  - Everett, 1979 -- 1990; MS055.002.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - (Everett) United States of America before the Federal Power Commission, 1977; MS055.002.004.00007 (Box 4)
  - (Everett) Cryogenic safety review, 1973; MS055.002.004.00008 (Box 4)
  - Great Meadows (1), 1970 -- 1993; MS055.002.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - Great Meadows (2), 1970 -- 1993; MS055.002.004.00010 (Box 4)
  - Hall's Brook, 1970 -- 1993; MS055.002.004.00011 (Box 4)
  - Horn Pond and Brook, 1970 -- 1993; MS055.002.004.00012 (Box 4)
  - Lexington, 1977 -- 1987; MS055.002.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Little Pond., 1970 -- 1993; MS055.002.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - Little River to Yates Pond, 1970 -- 1993; MS055.002.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - Malden, 1977 -- 1982; MS055.002.005.00004 (Box 5)
  - Malden River, 1970 -- 1993; MS055.002.005.00005 (Box 5)
  - Medford, 1976 -- 1984; MS055.002.005.00006 (Box 5)
  - (Medford) Wellington Station, 1976; MS055.002.005.00007 (Box 5)
  - Medford mercury poll reports, 1977; MS055.002.005.00008 (Box 5)
  - Middlesex Canal, 1970 -- 1993; MS055.002.005.00010 (Box 5)
  - Middlesex Fells, 1970 -- 1993; MS055.002.005.00011 (Box 5)
  - Mill Brook (1), 1970 -- 1993; MS055.002.005.00012 (Box 5)
  - Mill Brook (2), 1970 -- 1993; MS055.002.005.00013 (Box 5)
  - Mishawum (Woburn), Aberjona, 1970 -- 1993; MS055.002.005.00014 (Box 5)
  - Munroe Brook, 1970 -- 1993; MS055.002.005.00015 (Box 5)
  - Mystic Lakes and Dam (1), 1970 -- 1993; MS055.002.005.00016 (Box 5)
  - Mystic Lakes and Dam (2), 1970 -- 1993; MS055.002.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - Mystic River, 1970 -- 1993; MS055.002.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - Mystic River classification, 1970 -- 1993; MS055.002.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - Reading, 1977 -- 1982; MS055.002.006.00004 (Box 6)
  - Reed's Brook, 1967 -- 1988; MS055.002.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - Reed's Brook report, 1967 -- 1988; MS055.002.006.00006 (Box 6)
  - Somerville, 1973 -- 1988; MS055.002.006.00007 (Box 6)
  - Spot Pond and Middlesex Fells, 1967 -- 1988; MS055.002.006.00008 (Box 6)
  - Spy Pond (1), 1967 -- 1988; MS055.002.006.00009 (Box 6)
  - Spy Pond (2), 1967 -- 1988; MS055.002.006.00010 (Box 6)
  - Stoneham, 1980 -- 1981; MS055.002.006.00011 (Box 6)
  - Sweetwater Brook, 1967 -- 1988; MS055.002.006.00012 (Box 6)
  - Wakefield, 1967 -- 2001; MS055.002.007.00001 (Box 7)
  - Wedge Pond, Horn Pond Brook, 1967 -- 1988; MS055.002.007.00002 (Box 7)
  - Wellington Brook, 1967 -- 1988; MS055.002.007.00003 (Box 7)
  - Wilmington, 1979 -- 1982; MS055.002.007.00004 (Box 7)
  - Winchester, 1976 -- 1991; MS055.002.007.00005 (Box 7)
  - Woburn, 1976 -- 1995; MS055.002.007.00006 (Box 7)
  - Woburn hazardous waste sites (1), 1981 -- 1989; MS055.002.007.00007 (Box 7)
  - Woburn hazardous waste sites (2), 1980 -- 1989; MS055.002.007.00008 (Box 7)
  - Woburn industriplex (1), 1985 -- 1989; MS055.002.007.00009 (Box 7)
  - Woburn industriplex (2), 1971 -- 1989; MS055.002.007.00010 (Box 7)
  - Area-wide permitting strategy report, TeleCom City Rizzo Associates, Inc. [Binder], 2001; MS055.002.046.00001 (Box 46)
  - Archstone Woburn, Carmbridge Street, Woburn Massachusetts, 2000; MS055.002.046.00002 (Box 46)
  - Baywatchers II nutrient related water quality of Buzzards Bay embayments: a synthesis of Baywatchers monitoring, 1999; MS055.002.046.00003 (Box 46)
  - Belmont Day School, architectural plants, 2001; MS055.002.046.00004 (Box 46)
  - BRP WW01 Waterways Permit (chapter 91) [Binder], 1999; MS055.002.046.00005 (Box 46)
  - Burlington Office Park I Phase 2 [Binder] 1 of 2, 2000; MS055.002.046.00006 (Box 46)
  - Burlington Office Park I Phase 2 [Binder] 2of 2, 2000; MS055.002.046.00007 (Box 46)
  - Cambridge Park Drive area drainage project, response to comments on the notice of intent. Contents and sections 1-4 Part 1 of 2 [Binder], 2004; MS055.002.046.00008 (Box 46)
  - Cambridge Park Drive area drainage project, response to comments on the notice of intent. Appendices A- E Part 2 of 2 [Binder], 2004; MS055.002.046.00009 (Box 46)
  - Cape Cod Remediation Area, Mystic View road, Everett Massachusetts. 1 of 3 [Binder], 2000; MS055.002.046.00010 (Box 46)
  - Cape Cod Remediation Area, Mystic View road, Everett Massachusetts. 2 of 3 [Binder], 2000; MS055.002.046.00011 (Box 46)
  - Cape Cod Remediation Area, Mystic View road, Everett Massachusetts. 3 of 3 [Binder], 2000; MS055.002.046.00012 (Box 46)
  - Citizen appeal of proposed detention basin and related culverts with the Cambridge Park area of Cambridge, 2004; MS055.002.046.00013 (Box 46)
  - Clean Water action plan: restoring and protecting America's waters, 1998; MS055.002.046.00014 (Box 46)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, Vol. I, table of contents and reader's guide, part 1 of 6 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.046.00015 (Box 46)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, Vol. I, table of contents and reader's guide, part 2 of 6 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.046.00016 (Box 46)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, Vol. I, table of contents and reader's guide, part 3 of 6 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.046.00017 (Box 46)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, Vol. I, table of contents and reader's guide, part 4 of 6 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.046.00018 (Box 46)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, Vol. I, table of contents and reader's guide, part 5 of 6 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.046.00019 (Box 46)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, Vol. I, table of contents and reader's guide, part 6 of 6 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.046.00020 (Box 46)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol II, evalutation of project alternatives and Four Point Channel Storage Conduit, part 1 of 8 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.046.00021 (Box 46)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol II, evalutation of project alternatives and Four Point Channel Storage Conduit, part 2 of 8 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.046.00022 (Box 46)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol II, evalutation of project alternatives and Four Point Channel Storage Conduit, part 3 of 8 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.046.00023 (Box 46)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol II, evalutation of project alternatives and Four Point Channel Storage Conduit, part 4 of 8 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.046.00024 (Box 46)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol II, evalutation of project alternatives and Four Point Channel Storage Conduit, part 5 of 8 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.046.00025 (Box 46)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol II, evalutation of project alternatives and Four Point Channel Storage Conduit, part 6 of 8 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.046.00026 (Box 46)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol II, evalutation of project alternatives and Four Point Channel Storage Conduit, part 7 of 8 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.046.00027 (Box 46)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol II, evalutation of project alternatives and Four Point Channel Storage Conduit, part 8 of 8 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.046.00028 (Box 46)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol III, evalutation of project alternatives and Union Park detention/treatment facility, part 1 of 5 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.046.00029 (Box 46)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol III, evalutation of project alternatives and Union Park detention/treatment facility, part 2 of 5 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.046.00030 (Box 46)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol III, evalutation of project alternatives and Union Park detention/treatment facility, part 3 of 5 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.046.00031 (Box 46)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol III, evalutation of project alternatives and Union Park detention/treatment facility, part 4 of 5 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.046.00032 (Box 46)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol III, evalutation of project alternatives and Union Park detention/treatment facility, part 5 of 5 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.046.00033 (Box 46)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol. IV, recommended CSO control plan and projects not subject to facilities plan/env. review. part 1 of 6 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.046.00034 (Box 46)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol. IV, recommended CSO control plan and projects not subject to facilities plan/env. review. part 2 of 6 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.046.00035 (Box 46)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol. IV, recommended CSO control plan and projects not subject to facilities plan/env. review. part 3 of 6 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.046.00036 (Box 46)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol. IV, recommended CSO control plan and projects not subject to facilities plan/env. review. part 4 of 6 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.046.00037 (Box 46)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol. IV, recommended CSO control plan and projects not subject to facilities plan/env. review. part 5 of 6 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.046.00038 (Box 46)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol. IV, recommended CSO control plan and projects not subject to facilities plan/env. review. part 1 of 4 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.047.00001 (Box 47)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol. IV, recommended CSO control plan and projects not subject to facilities plan/env. review. part 2 of 4 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.047.00002 (Box 47)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol. IV, recommended CSO control plan and projects not subject to facilities plan/env. review. part 3 of 4 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.047.00003 (Box 47)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol. IV, recommended CSO control plan and projects not subject to facilities plan/env. review. part 4 of 4 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.047.00004 (Box 47)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol. V, appendices. part 1 of 6 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.047.00005 (Box 47)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol. V, appendices. part 2 of 6 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.047.00006 (Box 47)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol. V, appendices. part 3 of 6 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.047.00007 (Box 47)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol. V, appendices. part 4 of 6 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.047.00008 (Box 47)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol. V, appendices. part 5 of 6 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.047.00009 (Box 47)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol. V, appendices. part 6 of 6 [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.047.00010 (Box 47)
  - Concord-Alewife Rezoning Petition [Binder], 2005; MS055.002.047.00011 (Box 47)
  - Cottage farm CSO facility assessment report, introduction, contents, and executive summary. part 1 of 8 [Binder], 2004; MS055.002.047.00012 (Box 47)
  - Cottage farm CSO facility assessment report, sections1-3. part 2 of 8 [Binder], 2004; MS055.002.047.00013 (Box 47)
  - Cottage farm CSO facility assessment report, sections4-6. part 3 of 8 [Binder], 2004; MS055.002.047.00014 (Box 47)
  - Cottage farm CSO facility assessment report, sections 7. part 4 of 8 [Binder], 2004; MS055.002.047.00015 (Box 47)
  - Cottage farm CSO facility assessment report, sections 8-9. part 5 of 8 [Binder], 2004; MS055.002.047.00016 (Box 47)
  - Cottage farm CSO facility assessment report, appendices A and B. part 6 of 8 [Binder], 2004; MS055.002.047.00017 (Box 47)
  - Cottage farm CSO facility assessment report, appendices C-F. part 7 of 8 [Binder], 2004; MS055.002.047.00018 (Box 47)
  - Cottage farm CSO facility assessment report, appendices G-H. part 8 of 8 [Binder], 2004; MS055.002.047.00019 (Box 47)
  - Delineating bordering vegetated wetlands, 1995; MS055.002.047.00020 (Box 47)
  - Distribution and potential for adverse biologicfal effects of inorganic elements and organic compounds in bottom sediment, lower Charles River, Massachusetts, 2000; MS055.002.047.00021 (Box 47)
  - Draft Environmental Impact Report [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.047.00022 (Box 47)
  - Draft Environmental Impact Report Vol. 1 Belmont office/ R&D Building. 1 of 2, 2003; MS055.002.047.00023 (Box 47)
  - Draft Environmental Impact Report Vol. 1 Belmont office/ R&D Building. 2 of 2 [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.047.00024 (Box 47)
  - Draft Environmental Impact Report Vol. II Appendices. Archestone Woburn. 1 of 2 [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.047.00025 (Box 47)
  - Draft Environmental Impact Report Vol. II Appendices. Archestone Woburn. 2 of 2 [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.047.00026 (Box 47)
  - An ecosystem-based approach to urban and community forestry, 1994; MS055.002.047.00027 (Box 47)
  - Environmental Notification and Request for Waiver. Olin corporation [Binder], 2000; MS055.002.047.00028 (Box 47)
  - Environmental Notification From. Archstone Woburn, 2000; MS055.002.047.00029 (Box 47)
  - Environmental Notification From. Commercial Street, Beals Associates INC. [Binder], 2005; MS055.002.047.00030 (Box 47)
  - Environmental Notification From. Mugar Parcel, Rizzo Associates, INC. [Binder], 2000; MS055.002.047.00031 (Box 47)
  - Environmental Notification From. TeleCom City. [Binder], 1998; MS055.002.047.00032 (Box 47)
  - Environmental Notification From. The Jefferson, Allen and Major associates, INC. [Binder], 2000; MS055.002.047.00033 (Box 47)
  - EPA: Section 319 success stories, 1994; MS055.002.047.00034 (Box 47)
  - Expanded Environmental Notification Form. Redstone Shopping Center, Stoneham MA. Volume I of II. Appledore Engineering [Binder], 2005; MS055.002.048.00001 (Box 48)
  - Expanded Environmental Notification Form. Stoneham Plaza, MA. Volume II of II. Appendix. Appledore Engineering [Binder], 2005; MS055.002.048.00002 (Box 48)
  - Expanded Environmental Notification Form/Request for Phase 1 waiver. Cambridge Discovery Park. Acorn Park Holdings Realty Trust [Binder], 2004; MS055.002.048.00003 (Box 48)
  - Expanded Environmental Notification Form. the Village at Winning Farm and Murray Hills subdivision Woburn and Lexington, MA. 1 of 2 [Binder], 2002; MS055.002.048.00004 (Box 48)
  - Expanded Environmental Notification Form. the Village at Winning Farm and Murray Hills subdivision Woburn and Lexington, MA. 2 of 2 [Binder], 2002; MS055.002.048.00005 (Box 48)
  - The explorers guide to the Neponset River Watershed, 1997; MS055.002.048.00006 (Box 48)
  - Final Diagnostifc/ Feasibility Studey. HORN POND Woburn, MA, 1998; MS055.002.048.00007 (Box 48)
  - Final Diagnostifc/ Feasibility Studey. HORN POND Woburn, MA Appendices, 1998; MS055.002.048.00008 (Box 48)
  - Final Environmental Impact Report. Archstone Woburn, EOPA #12374. 1 of 2 [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.048.00009 (Box 48)
  - Final Environmental Impact Report. Archstone Woburn, EOPA #12374. 2 of 2 [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.048.00010 (Box 48)
  - Final Environmental Impact Report. Belmont Office/ R&D Building. [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.048.00011 (Box 48)
  - Final Variance report for Alewife brook and the Upper Mystic River. Contents, executive summary, and sections 1-3. 1 of 4 [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.048.00012 (Box 48)
  - Final Variance report for Alewife brook and the Upper Mystic River. sections 4-6. 2 of 4 [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.048.00013 (Box 48)
  - Final Variance report for Alewife brook and the Upper Mystic River. Sections 7 and appendices A-C. 3 of 4 [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.048.00014 (Box 48)
  - Final Variance report for Alewife brook and the Upper Mystic River. Appendices D-G. 4 of 4 [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.048.00015 (Box 48)
  - The Home Depot/ Parkway Plaza Shopping Center. Notice of Intent. BSC Group [Binder], 2004; MS055.002.048.00016 (Box 48)
  - Interim Data Submittal, Malden River Corridor [Binder], 2000; MS055.002.048.00017 (Box 48)
  - Massachusetts Water resources authority, 5 year progress report, 1995 -- 1999; MS055.002.048.00018 (Box 48)
  - Massachusetts Water resources authority, response to comments on the notice of project change for the long term CSO control plan forAlewife Brook. Introduction, contents and section 1. 1 of 6 [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.048.00019 (Box 48)
  - Massachusetts Water resources authority, response to comments on the notice of project change for the long term CSO control plan forAlewife Brook. Introduction, contents and section 2. 2 of 6 [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.048.00020 (Box 48)
  - Massachusetts Water resources authority, response to comments on the notice of project change for the long term CSO control plan forAlewife Brook. Introduction, contents and section 3. 3 of 6 [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.048.00021 (Box 48)
  - Massachusetts Water resources authority, response to comments on the notice of project change for the long term CSO control plan forAlewife Brook. 4 of 6 [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.048.00022 (Box 48)
  - Massachusetts Water resources authority, response to comments on the notice of project change for the long term CSO control plan forAlewife Brook. Appendices A and B. 5 of 6 [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.048.00023 (Box 48)
  - Massachusetts Water resources authority, response to comments on the notice of project change for the long term CSO control plan forAlewife Brook. Appendices C-E. 6 of 6 [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.048.00024 (Box 48)
  - Massachusetts Waterwatch, 1998; MS055.002.048.00025 (Box 48)
  - Massachusetts Wetlands restoration and banking program, newletter and notes, MS055.002.048.00026 (Box 48)
  - McLean Hospital, environmental consultant reports [Binder], 1997 -- 1998; MS055.002.048.00027 (Box 48)